RG 009:007, Indian Litigation Files
Connecticut State Library
- Series 4. Golden Hill Paugussetts, 1708-2006; bulk 1970-2006
  - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1708-2004
    - Exhibits in Support of Brief of the State of Connecticut in Support of Final Determination by the Assistant Secretary of the Interior for Indian Affairs Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussetts and in Opposition to Reconsideration, Volume I and II, dockets nos. IBIA 97-59-A, IBIA 97-60-A, 1997 April 25; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Exhibits in Support of Brief of the State of Connecticut in Support of Final Determination by the Assistant Secretary of the Interior for Indian Affairs Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussetts and in Opposition to Reconsideration, dockets nos. IBIA 97-59-A, IBIA 97-60-A, 1997 April 25; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Exhibits in Support of Brief of the State of Connecticut Regarding the Petition for Federal Tribal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Petitioner, 2001 September 17; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Exhibits in Support of Brief of the State of Connecticut Regarding the Petition for Federal Tribal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Petitioner, 2003 July 25 (Box 9, Folder 1-7)
    - Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, 2004 June 14-23 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Final determination - miscellaneous, 1994-2004 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - RE: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request for documents and comments submitted by the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests, circa 1993-2004 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Freedom of Information appeal exhibits and coercive litigation, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett appeal to Interior Board of Indian Appeals (IBIA), 2004 September 14 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Historic Contact National Historic Landmark Theme Study; Interiors Standards and Guidelines for Archeology and Historic Preservation, circa 1983-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
    - In RE Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Appendix to Brief of the State of Connecticut, 1997 April 25 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - In RE Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Appendix to Brief of the State of Connecticut, 2001 September 17 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - In RE federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Brief of the State of Connecticut, 1997 April 25 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - In RE Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Brief of the State of Connecticut in Support of Final Determination by the Assistant Secretary for Indian Affairs Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussetts and in Opposition to Reconsideration, docket nos. IBIA 97-59-A and IBIA 97-60-A, 1997 April 25 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - In RE Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Reply Comments Submitted Pursuant to 25 CFR 83.11 (f)(4) to the Secretary of the United States Department of the Interior Respecting the Petition for Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, IBIA 97-59-A and IBIA 97-60-A, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - In RE Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Response to September 17, 2001 Comments of the Connecticut Attorney General Respecting the Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
    - In RE Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe - Response to September 17, 2001 Comments of the Connecticut Attorney General Respecting the Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13-18)
    - Petition timeline, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion A, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion B, undated (Box 10, Folder 22-26)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion C, undated (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion D, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion E, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion F, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe: Proposed Finding - Summary Chart Criterion G, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Proposed finding - summary chart disks, 2002 June 14; 2 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Disk 1 and Disk 2 have been removed to Series 12. Removable Media
    - RE: The Connecticut Attorney General's Astounding Fifth Attempt to Flout Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA's) Rules by Submitting Additional Comments, 2001 September 20 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - RE: Golden Hill Paugussett Petition for Federal Acknowledgment, IBIA 97-59-A and IBIA 97-60-A, 1997 May 2 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
    - RE: Response of State of Connecticut to Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of Golden Hill Paugussetts, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - RE: Revised Residence Analysis for the Golden Hill Tribe of the Paugussett Nation, 2000 March 27 (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
    - Reconsideration of the Final Determination and Order Directing Full Consideration of the Documented Petition of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe under All Seven Mandatory Criteria, 1999 May 28 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Request for Review by the Secretary of the Interior of Order Issued in Reconsidered Final Determinatin in Golden Hill Paugussett Tribal Acknowledgment Proceedings, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
    - Response of the State of Connecticut in Support of Proposed Findings Against Federal Acknowledgment of Golden Hill Paugussetts, 1995 December 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Response to September 17, 2001 Comments of the Connecticut Attorney General Respecting the Petition for Federal Acknowledgment of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, 2002 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Secretary of the Interior decision on reconsideration request, 1998 December 22 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Supplement to the Documented Petition of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe for Federal Acknowledgment Submitted Pursuant to the Order of the Deputy Assistant Secretary for Indian Affairs of the United States Department of the Interior, Dated May 24, 1999, 1999 October 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Supplement to the Documented Petition of the Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe for Federal Acknowledgment Submitted Pursuant to the Order of the Deputy Assistant Secretary for Indian Affairs of the United States Department of the Interior, Dated May 24, 1999, Attachments, 1999 October 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - The Golden Hill Tribe of the Paugussett Indian Nation Supplement to Residence Analysis, Volume I, 2002 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
    - The Golden Hill Tribe of the Paugussett Indian Nation Supplement to Residence Analysis, Volume I - Overlay Map, undated; 1 volume (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - The Golden Hill Tribe of the Paugussett Indian Nation Supplement to Residence Analysis, Volume II, 2002 June 14; 1 volume (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Legal Documents, 1959-2006
    - Affidavit - Bayer, Aaron S., 1994 December 13 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Indian Tribe, et al. vs. Salti, et al., 1993 August 6; photocopies (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Indian Tribe vs. Town of Trumbull, CV 95 0327023S, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr., 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 31-34)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Appeal file, notes, and miscellaneous, circa 1997, undated; legal pad,; photocopies (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Brief of Defendant-Appellee with Attached Appendix, A.C. 17460, circa 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Brief of Plantiff/Appellant and Appendix, Golden Hill Tribe of Paugussett Indians, A.C. 17460, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Weicker, Lowell, Jr., CV 91 0500895S, Defendant's Response to Plantiff's Addendum, circa 1982-1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Defense Motion to Compel - Discovery Responses, 1994-1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, et al. vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Memorandum of Law in Support of Federal Defendant's Motion to Dismiss, 1993 January 4 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - miscellaneous, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - The Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - miscellaneous pleadings, 1994-2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - motion for extension of time, 1992 February 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - Plantiff's Appeal from Superior Court, A.C. 17460, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Weicker - pleadings, CV 91 500895S, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - privilege case law, circa 1959-1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe of Indians, et al. vs. M. Jodi Rell - miscellaneous pleadings, 2006 August 22 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous litigation, circa 1977-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Subject Files, circa 1789-2006
    - American Bar Association program on "the Gaming Law Minefield", 2005 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut Indian Affairs Council, 1973 September 13 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Federal Indian policy, circa 1790-2000; photocopies (Box 12, Folder 22-24)
    - Federal Tribal Government Recognition Process And Abuses in California, 2000 October 20 (Box 12, Folder 25-28)
    - Genealogy research, 2003 July 3; photocopies (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Genealogical research combined reports one through six, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 30-33)
    - The General Statutes of Connecticut, Revised 1958, Volume VIII, circa 1958-1959; photocopies (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett genealogical research combined reports one through six, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe of Indians vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr., 98-021 research, 1982-1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe of Indians vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr., Superior Court government correspondence - drafts, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Historical texts, diaries, GHP Fed BPT, circa 1789-1923; photocopies (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act (IGRA), circa 1988-2005 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Litigation Management Committee directive #5 memo, 1998 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Mashpee Tribe v. Town of Mashpee, et al., civil action no. 76-3190-S, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Office of Indian Affairs: Its History, Activities, and Organization, 1927; photocopies (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Oral argument - notes and materials, legal pad, photocopies, 1961-1998, undated (Box 13, Folder 3-7)
    - Research materials, circa 1850-2006 (Box 13, Folder 8-13)
    - Research materials - 200 Years of U.S. Census Taking: Population and Housing Questions, 1790-1990, 1989 November (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Research materials - appeal research, circa 1975-1997, undated; legal pad,; photocopies (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
    - Research materials - Bridgeport research, undated (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
    - Research materials - Bureau of Indian Affairs publications about American Indians, circa 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 21-23)
    - Research materials - Getting the Most Out of Genealogy with Computers, 2001 June 14 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Research materials - micellaneous, circa 1800-2002, undated; photocopies (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Research materials - motion to dismiss, circa 1975-1991; photocopies (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Research materials - motion to dismiss, circa 1950-1986, undated; photocopies (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Research materials - New Haven Colony Historical Society, circa 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Research materials - Overseer Reports, circa 1820-1890, undated; photocopies (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Research materials - records of the State of Connecticut, circa 1793-1993; photocopies (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Research materials - Smithsonian, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Research materials - Trumbull Tax Collector research, undated; photocopies (Box 14, Folder 6-9)
    - Research materials - Trumbull tax issues, circa 1900-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Research materials - Trumbull tax issue & Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information to state, circa 1860-1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Revised Residence Analysis for the Golden Hill Paugussett, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Settlement exception and definition, circa 1969, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Supplementary Documentation in Support of the March 1, 2000 Revised Residence Analysis for the Golden Hill Paugussett (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, circa 1991-2000
    - Correspondence - Attorney General, 1993-2000 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence - Babbitt, Bruce, Secretary of the Interior, circa 1991-1996, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe of Indians v. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr., 98-021, CV91-0500895-S, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Interior Board of Indian Appeals, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Reports, circa 1998-2004
    - Lobbying reports, circa 1998-2004 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Press Files, 1996-2004
    - Clippings, 1996-2004 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Maps, 1917-2003
    - Trumbull map, 2003 October 16 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Drawn May 1917 and revised February 1935 by L. D. Christie, last revised December 1960, 1917 May-1960 December; 20 maps, photocopies, 8.5 x 11 in.; 11 x 17 in.; Nichols Farm Burial Ground Association, Inc. (Box 81)
    - Planimetric Map of Town of Trumbull, Connecticut, Clarence F. Heiman - First Selectman, Trumbull, Connecticut, 1964; Compiled by photogrammetric methods by Abrams Aerial Survey Corporation, Lansing, Michigan, (Box 81)
      Sheet No. K-7
      Photography: 1964 April
      Mapping: 1964 October
- Series 5. Mashantucket Pequot, 1800-2007; bulk 1982-2007
  - E.P.A. Environmental Assessment, circa 1800-2007
    - Conversion to Trust of Six Lots North of Route 2, 1993 June (Box 14, Folder 23-26)
    - Deeds - Ledyard records, surveys, and maps, circa 1800-2007 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
    - Research materials, circa 1855-2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - E.P.A. Documents for Land Parcels, circa 1850-2007; bulk 1990-2007
    - Affidavit of Attorney Stephen J. Gray, Supervising Property Agent, Office of Rights of Way, Department of Transportation, State of Connecticut, 2007 November 5 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Coachman Pike 28, volume 411, page 918, 2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Coachman Pike 38, volume 282, page 704, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Coachman Pike 41, 49, 51-54, 56, 58-60, 64, 66, 67, volume 282, page 710, circa 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Coachman Pike 45, 47, 63, 65; Fanning 46; Shrewville 852R, volume 335, page 787, 2002; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Coachman Pike 55, volume 411, page 939, 2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Fanning 42, 48, 54, volume 282, page 699, 1992-1998; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Fanning 50, volume 217, page 392, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Indiantown 15, Shrewville 838R, volume 138, page 786, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Indiantown 38, volume 411, page 924, 2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Indiantown 39, volume 3, page 72, circa 1856-2007; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Indiantown 175, Route 2-39, volume 138, page 798, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1850-2004; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous - deeds, circa 1850-1984; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Route 2 # 3, 145A, volume 233, page 782, 1993, 2007; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Route 2 # 61, volume 411, page 934, 1969-2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Route 2 # 77, volume 217, page 400 and volume 152, page 670, 1986-2007 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Route 2 # 145, volume 225, page 30, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Route 2 # 145R, volume 217, page 395, 1992; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Route 2 # 161, volume 225, page 34, 1958, 1992; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Shewville # 770, volume 385, page 968, 2004; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Shewville # 806, Special Act 82-31, circa 1896-1982; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Shewville 812, 854, 858, 871, 875, 879, 899, 904, 929, 935, 938R, 943, volume 282, page 718, 1998; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Shewville 824R, 830R, 834R, 846, 886R, 916R, 928R, volume 138, page 879, circa 1865-2007; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Shewville 864, volume 138, page 809, circa 1984; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Shewville 882, volume 217, page 398, 1992; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Shewville # 882R, 838R, and 824R, circa 1971-2007 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Shewville 906, volume 411, page 929, 2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Shewville 908, volume 349, 2003; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Shewville 938, volume 385, page 973, 2004; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Tribal settlement boundary defined by Public Law 98-134, circa 2005; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 32)
      For map location see subseries Maps
  - Pequot Pharmaceutical Network, 1998-1999
    - Background, 1999, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Department of Social Services request for opinion on the Pequot Pharmaceutical Network, 1999 August 18 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Notes and memos, 1998, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Pequot Pharmaceutical Network - federal, circa 1999 July 30 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Related Attorney General opinions, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Statutes, 1999, undated; photocopies (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Subject Files, 1993-2001
    - Foxwoods Casino Environmental Assessment, 1993 May 6; photocopy (Box 15, Folder 40-41)
    - Attorney General's opinions on Mashantucket Pequot Gaming Commission Bill, 1995 March 22 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - State of Connecticut, et al. v. United States Department of the Interior, et al., 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2000
    - Correspondence - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 2000 March 6-8 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence - North Stonington, Ledyard, and Preston, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Press Files, 1999
    - Clippings, 1999 April-June, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Public relations announcements, 1999 April-May (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Maps, 1855-2007
    - E.P.A. Environmental Assessment
      Maps were removed from subseries E.P.A. Environmental Assessment
      - Plan made for State of Connecticut showing the reservation of the Easter Tribe of Pequot Indians, Town of North Stonington, Connecticut, 1963 January-February; 1 map, photocopy; Chandler & Palmer Engineers, (Box 81)
        Draw 1, Map 189
      - Plan showing property of Joseph A. & Gloria C. Roman in the Town of Ledyard, 1962 November 24; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 139
      - Town of Ledyard map showing land to be acquired from John A. Maher by the State of Connecticut, Route 2 (limited access highway), 1968 December; 1 map, photocopy, (Box 81)
        Sheet 1 of 3
        # 381
      - Town of Ledyard map showing land to be acquired from John A. Maher by the State of Connecticut, Route 2 (limited access highway), 1968 December; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        Sheet 2 of 3
        # 382
      - Town of Ledyard map showing land to be acquired from John A. Maher by the State of Connecticut, Route 2 (limited access highway), 1968 December; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        Sheet 3 of 3
        # 383
      - Plan showing parcel of land to be conveyed by Walter Domoracki, Sr. to Michael S. George, Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1970 September; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 441
      - Plan showing Miner Subdivision on property of Maurine B. & W Lawrence Miner, Jr., trustees, Connecticut Route 2, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1973 November; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 552
      - Plat of lands of George N. & Mildred H. Burns. Northeast of Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1974 July; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 596
      - Plan showing Section "D" of Stonehenge Development of Kenneth W. & C. Ann McBride, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1976 June; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        #676
      - Resubdivision plan showing Stonehenge Subdivision Section "G" property of Kenneth W. & C. Ann McBride. Coachman Pike (Pequot Trail) - Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1980 October; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 872
      - North Wind Hill Subdivision developed by Ronald O'Keefe. Fanning Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1985; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1155
      - North Wind Hill II Subdivision developed by Ronald O'Keefe. Fanning Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1985; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1156
      - Map showing land to be conveyed by the Town of Ledyard east of Shewville Road, 1986 March; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1225
      - Subdivision of land owned by Gussie Davis & Et al. 935 Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1986; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        Sheet 1 of 2
        # 1251
      - Subdivision of land owned by Gussie Davis & Et al. 935 Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1986; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        Sheet 2 of 2
        # 1252
      - Plan showing property belonging to the estate of George Henry Pratt Main situated between Indiantown Road, A.K.A. State Road 214, & Cider Hill Pentway, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1983 May; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1395
      - Plan showing Geer Resubdivision. Property of Kenneth J. Geer, Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1987 October; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        Sheet 1 of 1
        # 1406
      - Plan of land of Augustine W. and Evelyn F. Mazzalla showing tract to be granted to the Mashantucket Pequot Tribal Council, Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1987 August; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1426
      - Plan showing property of Mimi Abrams, Military Highway, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1988 March 27; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)
        # 1427
      - Plan & Profile shared access driveway property of Robert L. Day Co., Inc., Shewville Road, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1988 April 27; 1 map, photocopy (Box 83)
        # 1503
      - Plan showing land belonging to the Estate of George Henry Pratt Main located on Rote 2, (Norwich-Westerly Road), Lantern Hill Road, & Route 214, (Indiantown Road) in the Town of Ledyard, Connecticut, 1983 September; 1 map (Box 81)
    - E.P.A. Documents for Land Parcels
      Maps were removed from subseries E.P.A. Documents for Land Parcels
      - Plan showing tract of land owned by Nell Margaret Henkle, Ledyard, Connecticut, 1968 October; 1 map (Box 81)
        The map was removed from Box 15 Folder 11, "Indiantown 38, volume 411, page 924"
        # 350
      - Survey & plan of Pequot Indian Reservation in Ledyard, plotted by...Isaac Gallup, surveyor & committee, 1856 January 21; 1 map, photocopies; Gallup, Isaac, (Box 81)
        The map was removed from Box 15 Folder 12, "Indiantown 39, volume 3, page 72"
        Presented to the Connecticut State Library with the New London County Court records
        2 of 2 sheets
      - Assessor's tax map, Town of Ledyard, Connecticut, 1999 April 1; 1 map, photocopy (Box 81)